<!-- Plugin Configuration File. Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-configuration-file.html -->
<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.github.mallowigi.treehighlighter</id>
    <name>Project Tree Highlighter</name>
    <version>@version@</version>
    <category>UI</category>
    <vendor email="elior@material-theme.com" url="https://github.com/mallowigi">Pavel Barykin and Elior Boukhobza</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
        Highlights your project files and folders in colors.
        <br/>
        <br/>

        <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pnbarx/idea-treecolor/master/images/highlight-menu.png" alt="Highlight menu">
        <br/>
        <br/>

        When you are working on a large complex project you may need to highlight
        some of its parts in different colors.
        <br/>
        <br/>

        Previously, there was only one way to do this:
        create a scope, specify its name and filename pattern, then add a color
        and attach it to the created scope, then click <code>Ok</code> and <code>Apply</code>
        to see how it looks now. If the color doesn't fit, double-click it, select a new color,
        click <code>OK</code> and <code>Apply</code> again to see the changes. If the color
        doesn't fit again - repeat until it fits.
        This is a rather inconvenient way (and takes a lot of time).
        <br/>
        <br/>

        <strong>ProjectTree Color Highlighter</strong> was made to get rid of this inconvenience.
        Highlight your files and folders with ease using the context menu. Adjust the colors
        using the color picker, get an instant preview of the project tree and editor tabs
        while adjusting.
        <br/>
        <br/>

        <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pnbarx/idea-treecolor/master/images/color-adjustment.gif" alt="Color adjustment">
        <br/>
        <br/>

        All settings are persistently stored in the <code>
            <nobr>.idea/highlightedFiles.xml</nobr>
        </code>,
        so you can read and change it externally, clone or copy-paste to other projects, etc.
        (This allows you to create various project boilerplates with predefined highlighting settings.)
        <br/>
        <br/>

        <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pnbarx/idea-treecolor/master/images/config-file.png" alt="Config file">
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <br/>

        Enjoy and write a lot of awesome code!
        <br/>
        <br/>
        ]]></description>

    <change-notes/>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <incompatible-with>com.intellij.modules.rider</incompatible-with>

    <resource-bundle>messages.ProjectTreeBundle</resource-bundle>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">

    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>